So at this point, you've actually gathered
所以在这一点上 你实际上已经收集了
enough data to produce one of the goal visualizations,
足够的数据产生一个目标可视化,
to scatterplot with quadrants with audience score
用观众分数来散布情节
on the horizontal axis and critics score in the vertical axis.
在横轴上 评论家在纵轴上得分
Since this lesson is on gathering data,
因为这一课是关于收集数据的,
let's get past the assessing and cleaning steps of the data wrangling process,
让我们跳过数据处理过程中的评估和清理步骤,
which includes joining our two dataframes,
包括加入我们的两个数据站,
and let's flashforward to the final product, the visualization.
让我们来看看最后的成果 视觉效果
So here's what the data frame looks like with
这就是数据帧的样子
your newly gathered audience score and number of audience ratings.
你们新收集的观众分数和收视率
You can use matplotlib to create a simple visualization like this one,
你可以使用 matplotlib 创建一个类似这样的简单可视化程序,
a pretty basic scatterplot,
一个很基本的散点图,
but this is where something interactive like Tableau really shines.
但是这就是像 Tableau 这样的交互式作品真正闪光的地方
And here's what it looks like in Tableau. Pretty amazing.
这是它在 Tableau 的样子 非常惊人
So, you've got audience score on the horizontal axis ranging from 70% to 100%,
你可以得到水平轴上70% 到100% 的观众分数,
critics score in the vertical axis ranging from 91% to 100%,
评论家在纵轴上的得分从91% 到100% ,
well technically, 101, but that's just for visual purposes.
严格来说是101度 但那只是为了视觉效果
Then you've got these reference lines.
然后你就有了这些参考线
The vertical one being the median of audience score, which is 90%,
垂直的是观众得分的中位数 为90% ,
and the horizontal reference line is the median of critics score, 98%.
横向参考线是评论家得分的中位数 98%
In the top right corner of the screen,
在屏幕的右上角,
we've even got number of audience ratings and number
我们甚至有很多收视率和数量
of critic ratings represented visually, too.
评论家的评分也是直观的
Lighter shades of blue mean small number of
浅色的蓝色意味着少量
audience ratings and darker shades of blue means a larger number.
收视率和深色调的蓝色意味着更多的人
And smaller circles mean a smaller number of critic ratings
更小的圈子意味着评论家的数量更少
and larger circles mean a larger number of critic ratings.
更大的圈子意味着更多的评论家
And okay, so in the top right corner of the screen,
好的 在屏幕的右上角,
we've got universally loved movies.
我们有全世界都喜欢的电影
High audience scores, high critics scores.
观众得分高 评论家得分高
One of them being The Godfather, 1972,
其中一部是1972年的《教父》
which if we hover over this dot,
如果我们盘旋在这个点上,
we can see the 99% critics score and the 98% audience score.
我们可以看到99% 的评论家和98% 的观众
And in the bottom right corner,
在右下角,
we've got critically underrated movies.
我们有被严重低估的电影
Audience scores above the median audience score for this top 100 list
观众得分高于百强榜的观众得分中位数
and critics scores below the median critics score for this top 100 list.
评论家得分低于评论家得分中位数 排名前100
One movie being The Dark Knight,
一部电影是《黑暗骑士》
2008, audience score and critics score of 94%.
2008年 观众得分和评论家得分为94%
And in the top left, we have critically overrated movies.
在左上角 我们看到的是被严重高估的电影
Audiences didn't like these movies as much as critics did, basically.
基本上 观众并不像影评人那样喜欢这些电影
Compared to the median audience and critic rating,
与观众和评论家收视率的中位数相比,
the most notable point, 1940's, Pinocchio.
最引人注目的一点是1940年代的匹诺曹
A 100% critics score over 45 reviews but only a 72% audience score.
100% 的评论家评分超过45分 但只有72% 的观众评分
And then in the bottom left quadrant,
然后在左下象限,
we've got movies that didn't have
我们有一些电影
particularly high critic or audience scores in reference to the movies on this list.
特别是高评论家或观众的分数 参考这个名单上的电影
One notable one, Lala Land, 2016,
值得注意的是 《拉拉乐园》  2016年,
an audience score of 82% and a critics score of 92%,
观众得分为82%  评论家得分为92% ,
both well below the median scores for each.
都远低于各自的中位数
And here's E.T., right on the median critics score line,
这是 e.t 就在中间的评论家评分线上,
a 98% critics score and there's that low 72% audience score.
98% 的评论家得分 还有72% 的观众得分
So, this Best of Rotten Tomatoes critic versus audience score visualization
所以 这个烂番茄最佳评论家对观众得分可视化
required gathering data from two different sources: Accessing files on hand,
需要从两个不同的来源收集数据: 访问手头的文件,
and scraping data from web pages and that data was in two different formats,
从网页上抓取数据 数据有两种不同的格式,
a flat file, or a TSV file specifically,
一个平面文件 或者特定的一个 TSV 文件,
and HTML. Great job.
还有 HTML 干得好